

Contact

(C)

Phone

+91 81034 96299, 79993 82252



Website

https://vishalgoud.w3spaces.com



Email

vishalgoud81@gmail.com



Address

Vijay Nagar, Indore (M.P.), India

Social

@vishal_goud



Behance

@vishalgoud



Linkedin

@vishalkgoud

Languages

English

Conversational/Writing

Hindi

Native

Gujarati

Conversational/Reading

Education

• M.B.A. 2015-2017

Aasam Downtown University

• **B.com** 2000-2003

Devi Ahilya University

Certificates

• Green Box 2010 Frameboxx, Surat

Post Graduate Deploma in 2005
 Multimedia(PGDM)

Xplora Design Skool, Indore

Tools/Skills































Vishal Goud

UX UI Designer

Design Research	User Expe	erience	User Interface	e App Design
Ideation Wire	e Framing	Adaptiv	ve Web Design	Prototyping
Heuristic Evaluation	n			

About Me

I'm a Creative **UI & UX designer**, **HTML Developer**, and **WordPress developer** based in Indore (Madhya Pradesh) India. I having 12 years of experience in relevant field.

My expertise lies in conceptualizing and designing engaging software products that are both aesthetically appealing and highly functional. With strong problem-solving abilities and creative skills.

I am able to deliver effective "USER-FRIENDLY DESIGN" solutions that satisfy the needs of both the customer and the end-user.

Experience

• Sr. UX UI Designer

Imenso Software, Indore June 2017-Present

As a UI/UX design team lead, I am responsible for supervising the design process and ensuring the creation of visually appealing and user-friendly products for our target audience.

• Sr. UX UI Designer

Chapter247 Indore Dec 2016 to May 2017

As a Senior UI/UX Designer, my role involves designing user-friendly interfaces through research, wireframing, and collaborating with other teams to create visually appealing products.

• Sr. web faculty

Framebox Indore Sep 2015 till Dec 2016

I train individuals and teams in web design and user interface development, focusing on layout, typography, color theory, and imagery to improve the user experience and website effectiveness.

• Sr. Web Designer

MMF Infotech, Indore Aug 2014 till Sep 2015

I design user-friendly interfaces, conduct research, implement frameworks, and collaborate with cross-functional teams to create high-quality digital experiences as a Senior UI/UX Designer.

• Sr. UI/UX Designer

Engtelegent BPO Solution, Bhopal Oct 2013 to July 2014

As a Sr. UI/UX Designer, I am responsible for creating visually appealing and user-friendly interfaces, conducting user research, implementing design systems, and collaborating with cross-functional teams to deliver exceptional digital experiences.

Web Designer

WhitePaper, Indore Jan 2013 to Oct 2013

As a web designer, I have extensive experience in creating visually appealing and user-friendly designs for websites, mobile apps.

Web Designer

Webconnect PVT. LTD, Surat Jan 2012 to Dec 2012

As a web Designer, I am responsible for creating visually appealing and user-friendly interfaces, implementing design systems, and collaborating with cross-functional teams to deliver exceptional digital experiences.

• Web Faculty & head of Department

Explora Design Skool, Surat Sep 2006 to March 2011

As the web trainer and head of the department, I am responsible for overseeing the training and development of students in website design and maintenance. I also lead the department in developing and implementing strategies to optimize process.